<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>we are fenris on Fenris</title><link>https://gofenris.com/</link><description>Recent content in we are fenris on Fenris</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gofenris.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Privacy Policy</title><link>https://gofenris.com/privacy-policy/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gofenris.com/privacy-policy/</guid><description>Fenris is committed to protecting the privacy of visitors to our website. This privacy policy describes how we collect and manage information about you. This privacy policy is based on the digital impact toolkit.
When you visit or view gofenris.com, the site collects no personally identifiable information about you.
A cookie is set that expires at the end of the session. Server logs are maintained to protect the security of the site and to help improve the site by analyzing aggregate data.</description></item><item><title>The Data Leadership Cohort: Call for Participation</title><link>https://gofenris.com/post/data-leadership-cohort/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gofenris.com/post/data-leadership-cohort/</guid><description>Co-organized by Fenris, Digital Public and Aspiration, the Data Leadership Cohort (DLC) is an opportunity for peer learning for governance, stewardship and long-term responsible leadership in data-centric missions and ventures. Our first cohort launches in the first quarter of 2022.</description></item><item><title>COVID Modeling Accelerator</title><link>https://gofenris.com/portfolio/covid-modeling-accelerator/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gofenris.com/portfolio/covid-modeling-accelerator/</guid><description>&lt;h3 id="public-health-officials-need-better-data-driven-tools-to-make-critical-decisions-in-the-midst-of-the-pandemic">Public health officials need better data-driven tools to make critical decisions in the midst of the pandemic&lt;/h3>
&lt;figure class="db mh0 w-100">
&lt;img src="https://gofenris.com/images/cma_splash.png"
alt="Covid-19 Modeling Accelerator splash image"/>
&lt;/figure>
&lt;p>The COVID Modeling Accelerator was created to support a cohort of academic research teams to meet the needs of state and local decision-makers for actionable insights to better respond to the unprecedented challenges of the COVID-19 pandemic.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>eGUIDE Products for Energy Planning</title><link>https://gofenris.com/portfolio/eguide-api/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gofenris.com/portfolio/eguide-api/</guid><description>&lt;p>Fenris worked with the Electricity Growth and Use in Developing Economies (e-GUIDE) Initiative to help set objectives, design an approach and implement a first version of their public-facing API.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Data sharing for the Office of Recidivism and Justice</title><link>https://gofenris.com/portfolio/recidivism-data-sharing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gofenris.com/portfolio/recidivism-data-sharing/</guid><description>&lt;p>Fenris helped a California county office design governance and infrastructure to improve data collection, analysis and information sharing across agencies and contracted service providers towards improved reentry services and reduced recidivism.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://gofenris.com/about-section/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gofenris.com/about-section/</guid><description>Fenris is a consultant network founded by Aman Ahuja to support teams developing responsible data systems for public benefit.
We work to make these ventures successful and sustainable through collaborative co-design of product strategy, equitable data governance, and targeted technical assistance.</description></item><item><title>logo section title</title><link>https://gofenris.com/logo-section/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gofenris.com/logo-section/</guid><description>logos content</description></item></channel></rss>