<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>we are fenris on Fenris</title><link>https://gofenris.com/</link><description>Recent content in we are fenris on Fenris</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gofenris.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Product Strategy</title><link>https://gofenris.com/services/product_strategy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gofenris.com/services/product_strategy/</guid><description>We help teams create and utilize a product strategy that successfully bridges leadership vision with effective implementation. This ensures that effort is aligned with the desired impact, and that priorities and constraints across all functional teams inform milestones over time.</description></item><item><title>Technical Assistance</title><link>https://gofenris.com/services/technical_assistance/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gofenris.com/services/technical_assistance/</guid><description>We provide tailored technical support to address specific challenges, ensuring seamless integration and optimal performance of your data initiatives.</description></item><item><title>Data Governance</title><link>https://gofenris.com/services/data_governance/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gofenris.com/services/data_governance/</guid><description>We assist client teams in navigating data ownership, decision-making, stewardship, and other governance challenges essential for sustainable success in today’s data-driven landscape.</description></item><item><title>2024 in Review: Reflecting &amp; Refocusing</title><link>https://gofenris.com/post/wrapping-up-2024/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gofenris.com/post/wrapping-up-2024/</guid><description>Fenris has celebrated growth and opportunities in recent months, and collaborated with clients working on climate change, waste management, and food justice. As 2024 winds down, though, we are taking time to reflect not just on what we’ve accomplished, but on our mission. We are motivated to deepen our commitment to building a better, more equitable world.</description></item><item><title>The First Data Leadership Cohort Wraps Up</title><link>https://gofenris.com/post/data-leadership-cohort/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gofenris.com/post/data-leadership-cohort/</guid><description>Digital Public and Aspiration, the Data Leadership Cohort (DLC) is an opportunity for peer learning for governance, stewardship and long-term responsible leadership in data-centric missions and ventures. Our first cohort launches in the first quarter of 2022.</description></item><item><title>Privacy Policy</title><link>https://gofenris.com/privacy-policy/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gofenris.com/privacy-policy/</guid><description>&lt;p>Fenris is committed to protecting the privacy of visitors to our website. This privacy policy describes how this site collects and manages information about you, and how we use that information.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We hope this policy is clear and understandable. It is based on principles and templates provided by the &lt;a href="https://digitalimpact.io/">digital impact toolkit&lt;/a> and &lt;a href="https://tosdr.org">ToS;DR&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>When you visit or view &lt;strong>gofenris.com&lt;/strong>, the site collects no personally identifiable information about you.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We may use cookies for the purposes of web analytics and server logs. Web analytics and server logs are hosted on our own servers and related data are not shared with any third party services. Logs are purged periodically, approximately once a quarter.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The Data Leadership Cohort: Call for Participation</title><link>https://gofenris.com/post/dlc-cohort-cfp/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gofenris.com/post/dlc-cohort-cfp/</guid><description>Co-organized by Fenris, Digital Public and Aspiration, the Data Leadership Cohort (DLC) is an opportunity for peer learning for governance, stewardship and long-term responsible leadership in data-centric missions and ventures. Our first cohort launches in the first quarter of 2022.</description></item><item><title>logo section title</title><link>https://gofenris.com/logo-section/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gofenris.com/logo-section/</guid><description>&lt;p>logos content&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Who we are</title><link>https://gofenris.com/about-section/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gofenris.com/about-section/</guid><description>&lt;p>Fenris is a consultant network founded by &lt;a href="https://amanahuja.me" class="fa-red link dim" rel="noopener" target="_blank">Aman Ahuja&lt;/a>
 to support teams developing responsible data systems for public benefit.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We work to make these ventures successful and sustainable through collaborative co-design of product strategy, equitable data governance, and targeted technical assistance.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>